playdiplomacy.com 2019-02-19

# Play Diplomacy Online ::: web version of the classic Diplomacy board game

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [info@playdiplomacy.com](mailto:info@playdiplomacy.com).

At www.PLAYdiplomacy.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.PLAYdiplomacy.com and how it is used. 

**User information**  
We only store personal information which was entered by you, the user. This includes your chosen username, password, e-mail address and your real name, which is required at sign-up. This information is used purely for identification on the website. Only your username will be published online on our website, never your real name or e-mail address. We don't share any of your personal information with third parties. We hate spam as much as you. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other websites, www.PLAYdiplomacy.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies**   
www.PLAYdiplomacy.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Amazon.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.PLAYdiplomacy.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.PLAYdiplomacy.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.PLAYdiplomacy.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
